"use strict"


// **************PETER PAN TRIVIA  Q/A BEGINNER **************************
//     Be sure to enter correctAnswer based on index # in the array
var questions = [{
    question: "Where does Peter Pan come from?",
    choices: ["A) England", "B) Never Never Land", "C) South Central LA", "D) Fairyland"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "What were the names of all three children in the movie?",
    choices: ["A) Wendy, Steve, and John", "B)  Wendy, Michael, and Matt", "C) Wendy, John, and Michael", "D) DJ, Stephanie, and Michelle"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Aboard what type of vehicle do you fly in on the ride?",
    choices: ["A) Pirate Ship", "B) Rocket Ship", "C) Row Boat", "D) Monorail"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "What was the name of the children's dog?",
    choices: ["A) Rover", "B) Spot", "C) Nana", "D) Old Yeller"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Who pretended to be Captain Hook in order to get Smee to release Tiger Lilly?",
    choices: ["A) Wendy", "B) Peter Pan", "C) John", "D) John Stamos"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "What was the children's last name from the movie?",
    choices: ["A) Smith", "B) Johnson", "C) Trump", "D) Darling"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "Who warned Peter Pan not to open the present since it had a bomb inside of it?",
    choices: ["A) Tinkerbell", "B) Wendy", "C) Tiger Lilly", "D) Lady Gaga"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "What three ingredients does Peter Pan say are needed to fly?",
    choices: ["A) Snips and Snails, and Puppy Dog Tails", "B) Sugar and Spice, and Everything Nice", "C) Faith, Hope, and Love", "D) Faith, Trust, and Pixie Dust"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What happenend to Captain Hook's hand?",
    choices: ["A) Horrible shadow puppet accident", "B) He never had one", "C) Peter Pan cut it off", "D) He disobeyed his parents"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "True or False. Peter Pan's Flight was an original ride at Disney World and opened on October 3rd, 1971.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}];
